## **Juan Ortiz Beratto**

(347) 848-4854 | juanramon@rcn.com | www.linkedin.com/in/juan-ortiz-beratto-966424176 / | GitHub

#### **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Software Development Student with 10 years' experience in Electronic Engineering. Excellent communication skills and team player mentality able to provide different solutions to present issues. Ability to handle high pressure work bringing satisfactory outcomes to customers on time, and while maintaining strong attention-to-detail. Bilingual English & Spanish and Fluent in French.

### **Core Competencies:**

- Object Oriented Programming
- Customer Service
- Smart Phone and Web Design
- Interpersonal Skills
- Troubleshooting
- Electronic Engineering

## **EDUCATION**

## Queensborough Community College, Queens NY

**CUNY TechWorks Program, Expected Graduation Date:** 

Course Work:

- Web Client Programming
- Web Technology
- Creating Smart Apps

## San Juan National University, San Juan, Argentina

Master Degree in Electronics Engineering

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Languages: C++ | ES6 JavaScript | HTML 5 | CSS3 | JQuery | Bootstrap Frameworks/IDE: Sublime | Visual Studio Code/IDE | Atom | Notepad ++

Software: Microsoft Suite

OS: Linux/Ubuntu | Windows 7, 10 | Macintosh

Certication: CompTIA+

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Queensborough Community College, Queens, NY

Tech Internship

- Adding new courses (list name of courses) to the School Catalog
- Modifying courses content (explain in detail)
- Social Work on the College Campus (explain in detail)

#### Pier Sixty LLC, New York, NY

April 2003-Present

October 2018-Present

Bartender

- Ordering and maintaining inventory of bar products, including alcohol, drinks and supplies to ensure high volume of daily and weekly sales
- Ability to multi-task at a fast pace while dealing with various situations/individuals with over 1,000 customers weekly
- Interviewing and training new personnel

## **Atlantic Computer Services**, Hoboken, New Jersey

1994-1999

Field Engineer

- Repaired electronic devices such as monitors, printers, terminals and scanners; troubleshoot computers both Macintosh and PC compatible
- Assembled computers in large scale and design, repair and install networks
- Reviewed design drawings specifications and customer requirements for newly engineered components and processes

# INTERNATIONAL EXPERIENCE LVZ Informatics Company, San Juan, Argentina 1988-1993

Chief Engineer/ Manager

- Assisted and guided the customer updated systems and electronic devices
- Collaborated with electrical and mechanical engineers to resolve product development and maintenance issues